# EDWARD MANN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# EMAIL THE@EDDMANN.COM WEB EDDMANN.COM MOBILE 07517 335305

#### **PROFILE**

My passion is invested in the backend development and consumption of the web. Coupled with this, is the drive to make the next generation of desktop/web application using the latest development processes and ideologies. As a social person the team dynamic appeals to me greatly, giving me the opportunity to work with like-minded people. Through my present employment, since leaving University, I have had the chance to garner experience in both large (new startups) and small-scale (local businesses) application projects. In all scenarios I have invested personal time into researching and blogging about the latest best practices/technologies, which I then work hard to integrate into the development lifecycles I am apart of.

# **SKILLS**

Java Git • Unix • Unit Testing/BDD

PHP MySQL (Large Datasets) • ORM

Python Titanium • C# • CodeIgnitor

JavaScript HTML5/CSS3 • Bash/Zsh

#### **EDUCATION**

**BSc Internet Computing** 

2008 - 2011

University of Greenwich - London, England

1st Class Honours

\* school prize for outstanding achievement

BTEC National Diploma for IT Practitioners

West Kent College - Tonbridge, Kent

Distinction, Distinction, Merit

Secondary School GCSEs

Hugh Christie Tech. College - Tonbridge, Kent

14 Gained A\* - C

\* maths, english & science included

# **EXPERIENCE**

Atkins Global 2004

Work Experience

Robert Dyas 2006 - 2007

Part-time Sales Assistant

360 Software Solutions

**2011 - Present** 

Web Developer

# **INTERESTS**

As well as computing I have many other outside interests, these include:

- Exploring while travelling
- Playing basketball
- Listening to **podcasts**
- Watching football
- Driving in my car
- Black and white film photography

### REFERENCES

Available upon request.